A Guide to the Records of the Secretary of Technology, 1997-2006 (bulk 2002-2005)
Library of Virginia
- Series IV: Correspondence & Supporting Documentation, 2002-2005., Extent: 41 boxes. (Box 28-68)
  - Subseries B: Secretary's Correspondence, 2002-2005., 39 boxes (Box 30-68)
    - Sub-Subseries 1: Chronological Files, 1997-2005., 30 boxes (Box 30-59)
      - 2002
        - Correspondence - Outgoing
          - July (Box 36, Folder 8)
          - August (Box 36, Folder 9)
          - September (Box 37, Folder 1)
          - October (Box 37, Folder 2)
          - November (Box 37, Folder 3)
          - December (Box 37, Folder 4)
        - Defending the American Homeland (Box 37, Folder 5)
        - e58 Proposals (folder 1) (Box 37, Folder 6)
        - e58 Proposals (folder 2) (Box 37, Folder 7)
        - e58 Proposals (folder 3) (Box 38, Folder 1)
        - eGovernment Leadership-Realizing the Vision (Box 38, Folder 2)
        - eVa (Box 38, Folder 3)
        - Executive Orders & Legislative Studies Binder (Sections 1-7) (Box 38, Folder 4)
        - Executive Orders & Legislative Studies Binder (Sections 8-12) (Box 38, Folder 5)
        - Executive Orders & Legislative Studies Binder (Sections 13-16) (Box 38, Folder 6)
        - Executive Orders & Legislative Studies Binder (Sections 16-19) (Box 38, Folder 7)
        - Executive Orders & Legislative Studies Binder (Sections 20-21) (Box 39, Folder 1)
        - FACE International Corporation (Box 39, Folder 2)
        - General Assembly Session 2003 (HB 1530-HB 1957) (Box 39, Folder 3)
        - General Assembly Session 2003 (HB 2164-SB 1274) (Box 39, Folder 4)
        - George Washington University Virginia Campus (Box 39, Folder 5)
        - Gilmore Administration Briefing (Folder 1) (Box 39, Folder 6)
        - Gilmore Administration Briefing (Folder 2) (Box 39, Folder 7)
        - Governor's Advisory Board for the Virginia Biotechnology Initiative (Part 1-7) (Box 39, Folder 8)
        - Governor's Advisory Board for the Virginia Biotechnology Initiative (Part 8-10) (Box 40, Folder 1)
        - Governor's Higher Education Summit Steering Committee Meeting (Part 1-10) (Box 40, Folder 2)
        - Governor's Higher Education Summit Steering Committee Meeting (Part 11-19) (Box 40, Folder 3)
        - Governing Source Book (Box 40, Folder 4)
        - Hampton Roads Partnership (Box 40, Folder 5)
        - HJ 206 Report (Box 40, Folder 6)
        - Identity Theft Task Force (Folder 1) (Box 40, Folder 7)
        - Identity Theft Task Force (Folder 2) (Box 40, Folder 8)
        - Information Technology Association of America Board of Directors Meeting & Joint Board retreat (Box 40, Folder 9)
        - Information Technology: Challenges & Opportunities (Box 40, Folder 10)
        - Innovation U.: New University Roles in a Knowledge Economy (Box 40, Folder 11)
        - Integrated Criminal Justice Information System (Box 41, Folder 1)
        - Invented Here: The 2002 Southern Innovative Index (Box 41, Folder 2)
        - Joint Legislative Audit & Review Commission Development
          - Review of Information Technology Systems (Box 41, Folder 3)
          - Study of Workforce Training (Box 41, Folder 4)
        - Joint Venture: Silicone Valley Network (Box 41, Folder 5)
        - Latinos & Information Technology: The Promise & the Challenge (Box 41, Folder 6)
        - Mason Enterprise Center (Box 41, Folder 7)
        - National Electronic Commerce Coordinating Council (Box 41, Folder 8)
        - New River Valley Companies (Box 41, Folder 9)
        - Public Sector CXO Perspectives (Box 41, Folder 10)
        - Reform Agenda (Box 41, Folder 11)
        - Report on the Future of the South (Box 42, Folder 1)
        - Shenandoah Valley Technology Council (Box 42, Folder 2)
        - Speeches (Box 42, Folder 3)
        - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia (SCHEV) Strategic Planning (Box 42, Folder 4)
        - State of Innovation: Benchmarking Virginia's Performance in a Innovation-driven Global Economy (Box 42, Folder 5)
        - State Official's Guide to Internet Privacy (Box 42, Folder 6)
        - Surveys & Reports (Folder 1) (Box 42, Folder 7)
        - Surveys & Reports (Folder 2) (Box 42, Folder 8)
        - Surveys & Reports (Folder 3) (Box 42, Folder 9)
        - Tech Transfer 2002 (Box 42, Folder 10)
        - Tobacco Commission (Box 43, Folder 1)
        - Tobacco Commission e58 Task Force (Folder 1) (Box 43, Folder 2)
        - Tobacco Commission e58 Task Force (Folder 2) (Box 43, Folder 3)
        - University of Virginia Visit (Box 43, Folder 4)
        - VC 2002: The Premier Educational Conference for Private Equity (Box 43, Folder 5)
        - Venture Guide 2002 (Box 43, Folder 6)
        - Virginia Commercial Space Flight Authority (Box 43, Folder 7)
        - Virginia Commonwealth University (Box 43, Folder 8)
        - Virginia Economic Bridge (Box 43, Folder 9)
        - Virginia Economic Development Partnership (Box 43, Folder 10)
        - Virginia Performing Arts Foundation (Box 43, Folder 11)
        - Virginia Research & Technology Advisory Council (Box 44, Folder 1)
        - Virginia Workforce Council (Box 44, Folder 2)
        - Virginia Workforce Council Briefing Book (Box 44, Folder 3)
        - Working Council for Chief Information Officers (Box 44, Folder 4)
        - Working Council for Chief Information Officers - Organizing for Agility: Strategies for IT Efficiency & Continuous IT/Business Alignment in Uncertain Environments (Box 44, Folder 5)
      - 2003
        - Budget (Box 45, Folder 1)
        - Budget Action Reports (Box 45, Folder 2)
        - Center for Innovative Technology (Box 45, Folder 3)
        - Correspondence - No Response
          - January 2-20 (Box 45, Folder 4)
          - January 21-29 (Box 45, Folder 5)
          - February 3-20 (Box 45, Folder 6)
          - February 25-27 (Box 45, Folder 7)
          - March 5-7 (Box 45, Folder 8)
          - March 12-28 (Box 46, Folder 1)
          - April 2-8 (Box 46, Folder 2)
          - April 9-27 (Box 46, Folder 3)
          - April [Undated] (Box 46, Folder 4)
          - May 1-20 (Box 46, Folder 5)
          - May 21-30 (Box 47, Folder 1)
          - June 1-12 (Box 47, Folder 2)
          - June 12-30 (Box 47, Folder 3)
          - July (Box 47, Folder 4)
          - August 1-20 (Box 47, Folder 5)
          - August 21-28 (Box 47, Folder 6)
          - September (Box 48, Folder 1)
          - October (Box 48, Folder 2)
          - November (Box 48, Folder 3)
          - December (Box 48, Folder 4)
        - Correspondence - Response
          - January (Box 48, Folder 5)
          - February (Box 48, Folder 6)
          - March (Box 49, Folder 1)
          - April (Box 49, Folder 2)
          - May (Box 49, Folder 3)
          - June (Box 49, Folder 4)
          - July (Box 49, Folder 5)
          - August 1-12 (Box 49, Folder 6)
          - August 13-27 (Box 49, Folder 7)
          - August 29 (Box 49, Folder 8)
          - September (Box 50, Folder 1)
          - October (Box 50, Folder 2)
          - November (Box 50, Folder 3)
          - December (Box 50, Folder 4)
        - COVITS 2003 Event Program & Guide (Box 50, Folder 5)
        - Effective Use of Information Technology (Box 50, Folder 6)
        - eGovernment Leadership: Engaging the Customer (Box 50, Folder 7)
        - Eight Imperatives for Leaders in a Networked World (Box 50, Folder 8)
        - Federal Action Reports (Box 51, Folder 1)
        - HB 1530 & HB 1957 (Box 51, Folder 2)
        - Information Technology Association of America (ITAA) Board of Directors Meeting, 2003 May 4 (Box 51, Folder 3)
        - Information Technology Association of America (ITAA) Board of Directors Meeting, 2003 Nov. 9 (Box 51, Folder 4)
        - Information Technology Association of America (ITAA) Board of Directors Teleconference, 2003 Mar. 24 (Box 51, Folder 5)
        - Information Technology: Control Structures Are Only Part of Successful Governance (Box 51, Folder 6)
        - Institutionalizing IT Cost Efficiency (Box 51, Folder 7)
        - New Economy Strategies (NES) Presentation Materials (Box 51, Folder 8)
        - NIC eGovernment Leadership Summit (Box 51, Folder 9)
        - No Child Left Behind Act of 2001 (Box 51, Folder 10)
        - Outsourcing in Government: Pathways to Value (Box 51, Folder 11)
        - Secure Virginia Initiative (Folder 1) (Box 52, Folder 1)
        - Secure Virginia Initiative (Folder 2) (Box 52, Folder 2)
        - Tobacco Commission (Box 52, Folder 3)
        - VC 2003: Exploring the Business of Venture Capital (Box 52, Folder 4)
        - Virginia Research and Technology Advisory Commission (VRTAC)
          - Capitol Hill Day (Box 52, Folder 5)
          - Quarterly Meeting, February (Box 52, Folder 6)
          - Quarterly Meeting, October (Box 52, Folder 7)
          - Quarterly Meeting, November (Box 52, Folder 8)
          - Report Summary (Box 52, Folder 9)
          - Working Council for Information Officers (Box 52, Folder 10)
        - World Congress on Information Technology 2006 - Board of Directors Binder (Box 52, Folder 11)
        - World Congress on Information Technology 2006 - Board Meeting (Box 52, Folder 12)
      - 2004
        - Correspondence - No Response
          - January (Box 53, Folder 1)
          - February 2-17 (Box 53, Folder 2)
          - February 18-27 (Box 53, Folder 3)
          - March 1-3 (Box 53, Folder 4)
          - March 5-31 (Box 53, Folder 5)
          - April (Box 53, Folder 6)
          - May (Box 53, Folder 7)
          - June (Box 54, Folder 1)
          - July (Box 54, Folder 2)
          - August (Box 54, Folder 3)
          - October (Box 54, Folder 4)
          - November (Box 54, Folder 5)
          - December (Box 54, Folder 6)
          - Undated (Box 54, Folder 7)
        - Correspondence - Response
          - January (Box 54, Folder 8)
          - February (Box 54, Folder 9)
          - March (Box 54, Folder 10)
          - April (Box 55, Folder 1)
          - May (Box 55, Folder 2)
          - June (Box 55, Folder 3)
          - July (Box 55, Folder 4)
          - August (Box 55, Folder 5)
          - September (Box 55, Folder 6)
          - October (Box 55, Folder 7)
          - November (Box 55, Folder 8)
          - December (Box 55, Folder 9)
        - Globally Competitive South (Box 55, Folder 10)
        - Government Performance Project (Folder 1) (Box 55, Folder 11)
        - Government Performance Project (Folder 2) (Box 55, Folder 12)
        - Government Performance Project (Folder 3) (Box 55, Folder 11)
        - Marshall, Bob (Box 56, Folder 1)
        - National Engineers Week (Box 56, Folder 2)
        - Not Invested Here: The 2004 Southern Innovative Index (Box 56, Folder 3)
        - Report on Statewide Financial Management & Compliance (Box 56, Folder 4)
        - Shenandoah Telecommunications Company (Box 56, Folder 5)
        - Working Council for Chief Information Officers
          - Building the Secure Enterprise (Box 56, Folder 6)
          - Charting the Course for Principled IT Centralization (Box 56, Folder 7)
          - Informed Choices: Disciplines for a Business-Value Makeover in Corporate IT (Box 56, Folder 8)
          - Principled IT Expertise for End-to-End Business Organization (Box 56, Folder 9)
      - 2005
        - Commonwealth of Technological Opportunity: A Report Back to the Citizens of Virginia (Folder 1) (Box 56, Folder 10)
        - Commonwealth of Technological Opportunity: A Report Back to the Citizens of Virginia (Folder 2) (Box 56, Folder 11)
        - Correspondence - Incoming
          - January (Box 56, Folder 12)
          - February 1-24 (Box 57, Folder 1)
          - February [Undated] (Box 57, Folder 2)
          - March 3-14 (Box 57, Folder 3)
          - March 15-29 (Box 57, Folder 4)
          - April 1-25 (Box 57, Folder 5)
          - April [Undated] (Box 57, Folder 6)
          - May 4-19 (Box 58, Folder 1)
          - May 20-26 (Box 58, Folder 2)
          - June 1-30 (Box 58, Folder 3)
          - June [Undated] (Box 58, Folder 4)
          - July (Box 58, Folder 5)
          - August (Box 58, Folder 6)
          - September (Box 58, Folder 7)
          - October (Box 59, Folder 1)
        - Correspondence - Outgoing
          - January (Box 59, Folder 2)
          - February (Box 59, Folder 3)
          - March (Box 59, Folder 4)
          - April (Box 59, Folder 5)
          - May (Box 59, Folder 6)
          - June (Box 59, Folder 7)
          - July (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Sub-Subseries 2: General Assembly Information, 2003-2005., 7 boxes (Box 59-65)
      The General Assembly Information sub-subseries is housed in seven archival boxes and is arranged in chronological order by session, then alphabetically. This sub-subseries contains legislation, legislative study tracking reports, correspondence, bill summaries, memorandums, calendars of reports, status of studies, annual reports, operating plans, press releases, news clippings, drafting request forms, legislative action summaries, fiscal impact statements, enrolled bill reviews, electronic mail, and presentations. Noteworthy legislation includes the following: E-911 funds, consolidation of the Office of Secretary of Technology with the Secretary of Commerce & Trade (HB 1957); conflict of interest in contracts for research & development or commercialization of intellectual property (HB 2283); remote access to land records (HB 2294); telephone solicitors (HB 2311); fees collected by circuit court clerks (SB 740); workplace privacy (SB 1289); commercial electronic mail (SB 924); joint subcommittee to study the impact of collecting remote sales tax (HJR 176); telephone privacy act (SB 918); creation of the Virginia Information Technologies Agency (VITA) (SB 847 & SB 1247); Photogrammetrists bill, higher education bill (SB 1314); biotechnology partnership (HB 425); electronic meetings (SB 711); intellectual property (SB 1053); hydro energy plan (HB 2913); Technology & Biotechnology Investment Fund (HB 1692); Computer Crimes Act (HB 1729); and the Biotechnology Commercialization Loan Fund (SB 646).
      - 2003
        - Center for Innovative Technology (CIT) (Box 59, Folder 9)
        - Center for Innovative Technology (CIT) Budget Amendment (Box 59, Folder 10)
        - Dept. of Technology Planning (Box 59, Folder 11)
        - E-911 Funds (Box 59, Folder 12)
        - Enrolled Bill Reviews (Box 59, Folder 13)
        - Governor's Legislative Agenda (Box 59, Folder 14)
        - HB 1530 (Box 59, Folder 15)
        - HB 1575 (Box 59, Folder 16)
        - HB 1719 (Box 59, Folder 17)
        - HB 1761 (Box 59, Folder 18)
        - HB 1816 (Box 59, Folder 19)
        - HB 1925 (Box 59, Folder 20)
        - HB 1926 (Box 59, Folder 21)
        - HB 1927 (Box 59, Folder 22)
        - HB 1931 (Box 59, Folder 23)
        - HB 1957 (Box 59, Folder 24)
        - HB 2164 (Box 60, Folder 1)
        - HB 2283 (Box 60, Folder 2)
        - HB 2284 (Box 60, Folder 3)
        - HB 2285 (Box 60, Folder 4)
        - HB 2294 (Box 60, Folder 5)
        - HB 2311 (Box 60, Folder 6)
        - HB 2397 (Box 60, Folder 7)
        - HB 2426 (Box 60, Folder 8)
        - HB 2522 (Box 60, Folder 9)
        - HB 2523 (Box 60, Folder 10)
        - HB 2639 (Box 60, Folder 11)
        - HB 2721 (Box 60, Folder 12)
        - HB 2756 (Box 60, Folder 13)
        - HB 2760 (Box 60, Folder 14)
        - HB 2792 (Box 60, Folder 15)
        - Higher Education Issues (Box 60, Folder 16)
        - HJR 176 (Box 60, Folder 17)
        - House Appropriation's Committee Subcommittee on Commerce & Technology (Box 60, Folder 18)
        - Legislative Issues to Support Secretary Wood (Box 60, Folder 19)
        - Legislative Studies (Box 60, Folder 20)
        - Legislative Studies Follow-up (Folder 1) (Box 60, Folder 21)
        - Legislative Studies Follow-up (Folder 2) (Box 60, Folder 22)
        - Proposed Legislation (Box 61, Folder 1)
        - SB 740 (Box 61, Folder 2)
        - SB 795 (Box 61, Folder 3)
        - SB 796 (Box 61, Folder 4)
        - SB 847 (Box 61, Folder 5)
        - SB 873 (Box 61, Folder 6)
        - SB 874 (Box 61, Folder 7)
        - SB 875 (Box 61, Folder 8)
        - SB 918 (Box 61, Folder 9)
        - SB 924 (Box 61, Folder 10)
        - SB 925 (Box 61, Folder 11)
        - SB 942 (Box 61, Folder 12)
        - SB 1203 (Box 61, Folder 13)
        - SB 1247 (Box 61, Folder 14)
        - SB 1289 (Box 61, Folder 15)
        - Veto Session (Box 61, Folder 16)
        - VITA Bill (Box 61, Folder 17)
      - 2004
        - Broadband (Box 62, Folder 1)
        - General Assembly Session 2004 (Box 62, Folder 2)
        - HB 73 (Box 62, Folder 3)
        - HB 148 (Box 62, Folder 4)
        - HB 165 (Box 62, Folder 5)
        - HB 178 (Box 62, Folder 6)
        - HB 179 (Box 62, Folder 7)
        - HB 243 (Box 62, Folder 8)
        - HB 262 (Box 62, Folder 9)
        - HB 315 (Box 62, Folder 10)
        - HB 425 (Box 62, Folder 11)
        - HB 470 (Box 62, Folder 12)
        - HB 478 (Box 62, Folder 13)
        - HB 508 (Box 62, Folder 14)
        - HB 520 (Box 62, Folder 15)
        - HB 541 (Box 62, Folder 16)
        - HB 543 (Box 62, Folder 17)
        - HB 544 (Box 62, Folder 18)
        - HB 545 (Box 62, Folder 19)
        - HB 546 (Box 62, Folder 20)
        - HB 548 (Box 62, Folder 21)
        - HB 749 (Box 62, Folder 22)
        - HB 842 (Box 62, Folder 23)
        - HB 938 (Box 62, Folder 24)
        - HB 1000 (Box 62, Folder 25)
        - HB 1010 (Box 62, Folder 26)
        - HB 1040 (Box 62, Folder 27)
        - HB 1043 (Box 62, Folder 28)
        - HB 1145 (Box 62, Folder 29)
        - HB 1174 (Box 62, Folder 30)
        - HB 1201 (Box 62, Folder 31)
        - HB 1231 (Box 62, Folder 32)
        - HB 1281 (Box 62, Folder 33)
        - HB 1304 (Box 62, Folder 34)
        - HB 1330 (Box 62, Folder 35)
        - HB 1360 (Box 62, Folder 36)
        - HB 1380 (Box 62, Folder 37)
        - HB 1386 (Box 63, Folder 1)
        - HB 1389 (Box 63, Folder 2)
        - HB 1403 (Box 63, Folder 3)
        - HB 1467 (Box 63, Folder 4)
        - HJR 120 (Box 63, Folder 5)
        - HJR 176 (Box 63, Folder 6)
        - Joint Legislative Audit & review Commission (JLARC) (Box 63, Folder 7)
        - Legislation Action Summaries (Box 63, Folder 8)
        - Legislative Changes (Box 63, Folder 9)
        - Legislative Package (Box 63, Folder 10)
        - SB 11 (Box 63, Folder 11)
        - SB 95 (Box 63, Folder 12)
        - SB 151 (Box 63, Folder 13)
        - SB 161 (Box 63, Folder 14)
        - SB 171 (Box 63, Folder 15)
        - SB 182 (Box 63, Folder 16)
        - SB 241 (Box 63, Folder 17)
        - SB 302 (Box 63, Folder 18)
        - SB 539 (Box 63, Folder 19)
        - SB 565 (Box 63, Folder 20)
        - SB 598 (Box 63, Folder 21)
        - SB 646 (Box 63, Folder 22)
        - SB 688 (Box 63, Folder 23)
        - SB 1247 (also HB 1926) (Box 64, Folder 1)
        - Special Session (Box 64, Folder 2)
        - Veto Session (Box 64, Folder 3)
        - Virginia Biotechnology Partnership (Box 64, Folder 4)
        - Virginia Information Technology Transformation Project (Box 64, Folder 5)
        - VITA Bill (Box 64, Folder 6)
        - VITA Bill Amendments (Box 64, Folder 7)
        - VITA Legislative Proposal (Box 64, Folder 8)
        - Virginia research & Technology Advisory Commission (VRTAC) (Box 64, Folder 9)
      - 2005
        - HB 1572 (Box 65, Folder 1)
        - HB 1661 (Box 65, Folder 2)
        - HB 1691 (Box 65, Folder 3)
        - HB 1692 (Box 65, Folder 4)
        - HB 1729 (Box 65, Folder 5)
        - HB 1733 (Box 65, Folder 6)
        - HB 1801 (Box 65, Folder 7)
        - HB 1804 (Box 65, Folder 8)
        - HB 2051 (Box 65, Folder 9)
        - HB 2054 (Box 65, Folder 10)
        - HB 2151 (Box 65, Folder 11)
        - HB 2158 (Box 65, Folder 12)
        - HB 2395 (Box 65, Folder 13)
        - HB 2397 (Box 65, Folder 14)
        - HB 2404 (Box 65, Folder 15)
        - HB 2419 (Box 65, Folder 16)
        - HB 2470 (Box 65, Folder 17)
        - HB 2495 (Box 65, Folder 18)
        - HB 2534 (Box 65, Folder 19)
        - HB 2556 (Box 65, Folder 20)
        - HB 2586 (Box 65, Folder 21)
        - HB 2672 (Box 65, Folder 22)
        - HB 2753 (Box 65, Folder 23)
        - HB 2760 (Box 65, Folder 24)
        - HB 2797 (Box 65, Folder 25)
        - HB 2845 (Box 65, Folder 26)
        - HB 2860 (Box 65, Folder 27)
        - HB 2863 (Box 65, Folder 28)
        - HB 2866 (Box 65, Folder 29)
        - HB 2880 (Box 65, Folder 30)
        - HB 2908 (Box 65, Folder 31)
        - HB 2913 (Box 65, Folder 32)
        - HB 2924 (Box 65, Folder 33)
        - Legislative Package (Box 65, Folder 34)
        - Photogrammetrists (Box 65, Folder 35)
        - SB 711 (Box 65, Folder 36)
        - SB 879 (Box 65, Folder 37)
        - SB 882 (Box 65, Folder 38)
        - SB 902 (Box 65, Folder 39)
        - SB 959 (Box 65, Folder 40)
        - SB 960 (Box 65, Folder 41)
        - SB 963 (Box 65, Folder 42)
        - SB 992 (Box 65, Folder 43)
        - SB 1005 (Box 65, Folder 44)
        - SB 1027 (Box 65, Folder 45)
        - SB 1053 (Box 65, Folder 46)
        - SB 1107 (Box 65, Folder 47)
        - SB 1148 (Box 65, Folder 48)
        - SB 1159 (Box 65, Folder 49)
        - SB 1192 (Box 65, Folder 50)
        - SB 1196 (Box 65, Folder 51)
        - SB 1249 (Box 65, Folder 52)
        - SB 1252 (Box 65, Folder 53)
        - SB 1286 (Box 65, Folder 54)
        - SB 1306 (Box 65, Folder 55)
        - SB 1314 (Box 65, Folder 56)
        - SB 1327 (Box 65, Folder 57)
        - SB 1337 (Box 65, Folder 58)
        - Secretary of Technology Watch Bills (Box 65, Folder 59)
    - Sub-Subseries 3: Legislative Files & Information, 1999-2004., 3 boxes (Box 66-68)
      The Legislative Files & Information sub-subseries is housed in three archival boxes and is arranged in alphabetical order. This sub-subseries contains legislation, reports, correspondence, memorandums, presentations, and other sundry items. Significant is legislation concerning technology issues such as the Commonwealth Technology Research Fund, the Virginia Anti-Spamming Act, the Virginia Information Technologies Agency, and the Information Technology Investment Board.
      - Audit Reports, 2001-2003. (Box 66, Folder 1)
      - Budget Amendments, 2002. (Box 66, Folder 2)
      - Governor's Cabinet Secretary's Report on Audit, 2004. (Box 66, Folder 3)
      - House Appropriations, House Finance, & Senate Finance Committees, 2002. (Box 66, Folder 4)
      - Innovative Technology Authority Annual Financial Statements, 2004. (Box 66, Folder 5)
      - JLARC Interim Report, 2002. (Box 66, Folder 6)
      - Legislation, 1999. (Box 66, Folder 7)
      - Legislation, 2003. (Box 66, Folder 8)
      - Legislation, 2003. (Box 66, Folder 9)
      - Legislation, 2003. (Box 67, Folder 1)
      - Legislative Session 2002, 2002. (Box 67, Folder 2)
      - Legislative Session 2002, 2002. (Box 67, Folder 3)
      - Legislative Session 2002, 2002. (Box 67, Folder 4)
      - Legislative Session 2003 (Box 67, Folder 5)
      - Reports on Statewide Financial Management & Compliance, 2001-2004. (Box 67, Folder 6)
      - Review of the Dept. of Taxation Public-Private Partnership with American Management Systems, 2002. (Box 67, Folder 7)
      - Standards & Procedures, 2003. (Box 68, Folder 1)
      - Technology Investment Projects, 2003. (Box 68, Folder 2)
      - Technology Investment Projects, 2003-2004. (Box 68, Folder 3)
      - Technology Investment Projects, 2004. (Box 68, Folder 4)
      - Virginia Commercial Space Flight Authority Reports on Audit, 2002-2004. (Box 68, Folder 5)
      - Virginia Financial Perspective, 2001. (Box 68, Folder 6)
      - Virginia Information Providers Network Authority Report on Audit, 2003. (Box 68, Folder 7)
      - VITA Draft Operating Plan, 2003. (Box 68, Folder 8)